<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LaRoomy</string>
    <string name="app_version">App-Version 2.1.0</string>
    <!-- UI Strings -->
    <string name="MA_AvailableDevicesPresentationTextViewText">Devices</string>
    <string name="MA_NoAvailableDevices">No devices found. Please make sure the device is bonded to the system.</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_SettingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_InformationTitle">App-Info</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_HelpTitle">Help Topics</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_ShowLogTitle">Show Log</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_ReloadList">Reload List</string>
    <string name="MA_UserNotificationDialogTitle">Notification</string>
    <string name="MA_NoContentUserHintText">Nothing to show.\nAdd your first device.</string>
    <string name="MA_BluetoothNotEnabledHintText">The base functionality of this App is to connect to bluetooth devices. Therefore bluetooth must be enabled. Tap here to enable bluetooth.</string>
    <string name="MA_BluetoothPermissionMissionHintText">The base functionality of this App is to connect to bluetooth devices. Therefore it needs your permission to access bluetooth devices on this phone and connect to it. Tap here to grant the permission.</string>

    <string name="CA_Connecting">Connecting..</string>
    <string name="CA_Connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="CA_Initialize">Initialize..</string>
    <string name="CA_LoadingProperties">Loading Properties..</string>

    <!-- check if this is really necessary??? -->
    <string name="CA_AuthSuccess">Authentication success - Checking Device Properties</string>

    <string name="CA_BindingPasskeyRejected">Wrong binding-passkey: connection rejected</string>
    <string name="CA_BindingNotActivated">Binding required but not activated in App-Settings</string>
    <string name="CA_TimeoutForConnection">Timeout: Device not reachable</string>
    <string name="CA_ErrorDeviceListIndexInvalid">Invalid Device-List index</string>
    <string name="CA_ErrorDeviceAddressAccessException">Critical error. Index out of bounds.</string>
    <string name="CA_InitTimeoutOccurred">Timeout: Remote device not responding</string>
    <string name="CA_TransmissionTimeoutOccurred">Transmission timeout: Remote device not responding</string>
    <string name="CA_FirstTimeoutSecondTryout">Cannot connect to device. Trying again..</string>

    <string name="DMA_ConnectionStatus_disconnected">disconnected</string>
    <string name="DMA_ConnectionStatus_disconnected_tryToReconnect">disconnected - trying to reconnect</string>
    <string name="DMA_ConnectionStatus_connected">connected</string>
    <string name="DMA_Ready">Ready</string>
    <string name="DMA_DeviceConnectionSuspended">Connection suspended</string>
    <string name="DMA_LoadingPropertiesUserInfo">Loading Properties..</string>
    <string name="DMA_NoConnection">No connection</string>
    <string name="DMA_ErrorElementText">error:type !</string>
    <string name="DMA_PopUpMenuText_DeviceSettings">Device Settings</string>
    <string name="DMA_PopUpMenuText_DiscardDevice">Close Device</string>
    <string name="DMA_PopUpMenuText_ReloadProperties">Reload Properties</string>
    <string name="DMA_ReconnectDevice">Resuming Connection..</string>


    <string name="RGB_HeaderText">RGB Control</string>
    <string name="RGB_OnOff">On / Off</string>
    <string name="RGB_SingleColorModeButtonText">Single Color</string>
    <string name="RGB_TransitionModeButtonText">Transition</string>
    <string name="RGB_TransitionSpeedSeekBarText">Transition Speed</string>
    <string name="RGB_SoftTransitionSwitchText">Soft Transition</string>

    <string name="ELS_HeaderText">Ex Level Select</string>
    <string name="ELS_OnOff">On / Off</string>

    <string name="STS_HeaderText">Time Selector</string>
    <string name="STS_Hours">Hours</string>
    <string name="STS_Minutes">Minutes</string>
    <string name="STS_Seconds">Seconds</string>
    <string name="STS_TimePlaceholder">00 : 00</string>

    <string name="NavCon_HeaderText">Navigator</string>

    <string name="TFS_HeaderText">Time-Frame Selector</string>
    <string name="TFS_From">From</string>
    <string name="TFS_To">To</string>

    <string name="BarGraphActivity_HeaderText">Bar Graph View</string>

    <string name="LineGraphActivity_HeaderText">Line Graph View</string>

    <string name="StringInterrogatorActivity_HeaderText">String Interrogator</string>
    <string name="StringInterrogatorActivity_FieldOneDescriptorPlaceholder">Field 1</string>
    <string name="StringInterrogatorActivity_FieldTwoDescriptorPlaceholder">Field 2</string>
    <string name="StringInterrogatorActivity_ButtonPlaceholderText">Submit</string>

    <string name="TextListPresenter_HeaderText">Text List Presenter</string>


    <string name="UnlockCtrl_HeaderText">Unlock Control</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ConditionText_Locked">Locked</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ConditionText_Unlocked">Unlocked</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PinEntryText">PIN:</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ButtonText_Show">Show</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ButtonText_Hide">Hide</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PopupHeaderText">Change Pin</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PopupCurrentPinDescriptorText">Current Pin:</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PopupNewPinDescriptorText">New Pin:</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PopupRepeatNewPinDescriptorText">Repeat new Pin:</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PopupCancelButtonText">Cancel</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PopupPositiveButtonText">Change</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_LockHintMessageText">Tap image to lock</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PinChangeFailedWrongPin">Pin change failed - wrong pin.</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PinChangeSuccess">Pin changed successful.</string>


    <string name="GeneralMessage_reconnected">Device reconnected</string>
    <string name="GeneralMessage_connectionSuspended">Connection suspended</string>
    <string name="GeneralMessage_resumingConnection">Resuming connection - please wait</string>
    <string name="GeneralMessage_connectingFailed">Connection failed:</string>
    <string name="GeneralString_OK">OK</string>
    <string name="GeneralString_Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="GeneralString_UnexpectedConnectionLossMessage">The connection was interrupted. Try to connect again?</string>
    <string name="GeneralString_ConnectionLossDialogTitle">Connection Error</string>


    <string name="InfoActivity_HeaderText">LaRoomy</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_AppDescription">Dynamic Remote Control</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_AppVersionEntry">App-Version </string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CopyrightLaroomySoft">&#169; 2022 Hans Philipp Zimmermann</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CEOHansZimmermann">CEO Hans Philipp Zimmermann</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_AllRightsReserved">All rights reserved</string>

    <string name="InfoActivity_ImprintAndContact">Imprint &amp; Contact</string>

    <string name="InfoActivity_MailTo">info@laroomy.de</string>

    <string name="InfoActivity_PrivacyPolicyHeader">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PrivacyPolicy_Text">Hans Philipp Zimmermann built the LaRoomy app as a free app. This SERVICE is provided by Hans Philipp Zimmermann at no cost and is intended for use as is.This page is used to inform users regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service. If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_InformationCollectionAndUse_Header">Information Collection and Use</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_InformationCollectionAndUse_Text">The app does not collect any personal data. But the app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ThirdPartyServiceLink_one">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LogDataHeader">Log Data</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LogDataText">I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LinksToOtherSitesHeader">Links to Other Sites</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LinksToOtherSitesText">This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ChangesToThisPrivacyPolicyHeader">Changes to This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ChangesToThisPrivacyPolicyText">I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. This policy is effective as of 2020&#8211;09&#8211;09</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ContactUsHeader">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ContactUsText">If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at info@laroomy.de.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_HeaderText">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_FirstChapter">By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also should not try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Hans Philipp Zimmermann. Hans Philipp Zimmermann is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for. The LaRoomy app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, in order to provide my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the LaRoomy app won’t work properly or at all. The app does use third party services that declare their own Terms and Conditions. Link to Terms and Conditions of third party service providers used by the app:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_SecondChapter">You should be aware that there are certain things that Hans Philipp Zimmermann will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but Hans Philipp Zimmermann cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left. If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app. Along the same lines, Hans Philipp Zimmermann cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Hans Philipp Zimmermann cannot accept responsibility. With respect to Hans Philipp Zimmermann’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Hans Philipp Zimmermann accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app. At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Hans Philipp Zimmermann does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ChangesToThisTermsHeaderText">Changes to this Terms and Conditions</string>
    +
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ChangesToThisTermsContentText">I may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page. These terms and conditions are effective as of 2020–09–09</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ContactHeaderText">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ContactContentText">If you have any questions or suggestions about my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact me at info@laroomy.de.</string>

    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_HeaderText">Credits</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_StartText">This project is using some open-source libraries. Here you can find a list of all programmers and/or companies which provisions contributed to this app.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_ThankYouHeaderText">My biggest thanks goes to:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_SpinKit_Thx">Ybq - for the fantastic SpinKit Library.\nAmazing Android loading animations:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_SpinKit_ActionLinkText">Show source and license on GitHub</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_ColorPicker_Thx">QuadFlask - for the gorgeous ColorPicker.\nAndroid color picker with color wheel and lightness bar</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_ColorPicker_ActionLinkText">Show source and licence on Github</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_FluidSlider_Thx">Ramotion - for the fancy Fluid-Slider.\nA slider widget with a popup bubble displaying the precise value:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_FluidSlider_ActionLinkText">Show source and licence on Github</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CR_FluidSlider_RamotionBackLinkText">www.Ramotion.com</string>

    <string name="InfoActivity_RS_HeaderText">Documentation &amp; Resources</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_Disclaimer_HeaderText">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_Disclaimer_Text">The author of this program is not liable for damages to software or hardware or property damage resulting from the use of the program. The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the provided application. Liability claims against the author, which relate to damages of material or ideal kind, caused by the use of the presented application, are fundamentally excluded, as long as the author has no proven intentional or grossly negligent fault.</string>

    <string name="SetupActivity_Header">Settings</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_AutoConnectElementText">Auto-Connect</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_AutoConnectHint">If auto-connect is set up, the app will try to connect to the last device on startup. If only one device is available, the app connects automatically to this device.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_CustomBindingCodeElementText">Use custom binding key</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_CustomBindingCodeHint">By default a random generated binding-code is used. To use your own key, set it up here.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_BindingCodeDescriptor">Binding-Code</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_SavePropertiesElementText">Save Device-Properties</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_SavePropertiesHint">If activated, the device-properties for the connected remote device will be saved. This results in a faster connection performance.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_UUIDManagerButtonText">Manage UUID-Profiles</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_EnableLoggingElementText">Enable Connection Log</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_EnableLoggingHint">All transmission-data and connection-events will be saved to a temporary cache. This may reduce the performance in the connection process but could be helpful for troubleshooting or during the development process of the remote device.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_ShowLogButtonText">Show Log</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_PassKeyMustNotBeEmpty">Binding Code cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_PassKeyMaxIs10Character">The maximum length of the binding-code is 10 character.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_PassKeyContainsInvalidCharacter">The binding-code contains invalid character.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_ResetDataButtonText">Reset App Data</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_KeepScreenActiveElementText">Keep screen active</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_KeepScreenActiveHint">Prevents the device from falling in sleep-mode when the remote device is connected.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_BindingManagerButtonText">Binding-Data Manager</string>

    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_HeaderText">Manage Binding-Data</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_BindingTypeAsOriginator">Origin</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_BindingTypeDeprecatedOriginator">Origin (Key deprecated)</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_BindingTypeAsSharingReceiver">Shared Key</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_ListElementDeviceName">Device-Name:</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_ListElementMacAddress">Mac-Address:</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_ListElementBindingType">Binding-Type:</string>
    <string name="BindingManagerActivity_UserHint">Swipe left to delete a data set. Be careful: if binding is activated on a specific device, the connection may be fail. Make sure to release binding before deleting the appropriate data set.</string>

    <string name="ResetAppActivity_HeaderText">Reset Data</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_SelectDataActionText">Select the data you want to reset:</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_SelectAllCheckBoxText">Select all</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetAppSettingsCheckBoxText">App Settings</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetBindingDataCheckBoxText">Binding Data</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetUUIDProfilesCheckBoxText">UUID Profiles</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetDefaultBindingKeyCheckBoxText">Default Binding Key</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetAppSettingsCheckBoxHint">The common app settings will be set to default.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetBindingDataCheckBoxHint">All data regarding the device-binding will be deleted. Including the shared binding data.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetUUIDProfilesCheckBoxHint">All UUID-Profiles will be deleted. Except the static profiles.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetDefaultBindingKeyCheckBoxHint">A new custom Binding-Key will be generated. Be careful if there are remote devices which require the current Key.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetPropertyCacheCheckboxText">Property Cache</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetPropertyCacheCheckboxHint">The saved properties for all devices will be cleared.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_CancelButtonText">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetButtonText">Reset</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_NoDataSelected">No data selected.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogMessage">The selected data will be deleted or restored to default.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogTitle">Reset</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogPositiveButtonText">OK</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogNegativeButtonText">Cancel</string>


    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_HeaderText">Device-Settings</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_UserInfo_Connected">Device Connected</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_UserInfo_Disconnected">Device Disconnected</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingSwitchDescriptor">Device-Binding active</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingPurposeHint">If binding is enabled, the remote device is linked to this app and does not accept other connections. To provide access to the device for other users, the binding could be shared.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetButtonDescriptorText">Factory Reset</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetButtonText">Reset</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetConfirmationMessage">The remote device will be restored to the default configuration. Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ShareButtonDescriptorText">Share Device-Binding</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ShareButtonHint">The binding information for this specific device will be shared. The data will be encrypted and your binding-code is not visible to the receiver or someone else.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetHint">A factory-reset-command will be sent to the remote device.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingNotSupportedNotification">The connected device does not support binding.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_OnlyTheOriginCanShareTheBindingNotification">The connection with this device is established with a shared binding-key. Sharing a shared key is not possible, only the originator is able to share the binding.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_OnlyTheOriginCanReleaseTheBinding">The connection with this device is established with a shared binding-key. Only the originator is able to release the binding.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingSuccessNotification">Binding successful generated.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingErrorNotification">Binding failure. Error occurred on the device.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceInfoHeaderText"><u>Device Info:</u></string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceInfoNameDescriptorText">Name:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceMACAddressDescriptorText">MAC:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceServiceUUIDDescriptorText">Service UUID:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceRxCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">RX Characteristic UUID:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceTxCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">TX Characteristic UUID:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ReleaseBindingSuccessText">Binding successful released.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ReleaseBindingFailedWrongPasskeyText">Release binding failed. Wrong passkey!</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ReleaseBindingFailedUnknownErrorText">Release binding failed. Unknown error!</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ShowDeviceInfoButtonText">Show device info</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingNotConfirmed">No response received from remote device. Binding not confirmed.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ReleaseNotConfirmed">No response received from remote device. Release of device-binding not confirmed.</string>


    <string name="AppHelpActivityHeaderText">Help-Topics</string>

    <string name="AppHelpTopic_TheConceptShortExplained_Header">The concept short explained</string>
    <string name="AppHelpTopic_TheConceptShortExplained_P1">Different peripheral Bluetooth-devices require specific user-interfaces which are tailor-made for the particular hardware of the device. Therefore a purpose-made app is required for every device. The LaRoomy app provides a dynamic user-interface and is capable to adapt to the properties of a particular device. By implementing the LaRoomy transmission-protocol, every device with Bluetooth-GATT connectivity can be used in conjunction with the LaRoomy app. The creation and provisioning of a specific app for a device is not necessary and the implementation and control via Bluetooth can be provided quickly and efficiently.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpTopic_TheConceptShortExplained_P3">Devices with implementation of the transmission protocol can transmit their capabilities (device-properties) at the beginning of the connection process. The app will show the appropriate control elements in alignment to the properties of the device. The visual state of the app is different for devices with different device-properties. This allows a wide support of device-types and applications providing a clean user-interface without unnecessary control elements.</string>

    <string name="AppHelpTopic_ConnectDevice">Add a new device</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P1">1. Launch the LaRoomy app or navigate to the start page.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P2">2. Tap the add button in the upper right corner.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P3">3. A list with all paired devices will be shown.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_BondingHint">The device must be bonded with the system. If the desired device is not located in the list, tap on the lower banner to navigate to the bluetooth settings where you can scan for devices. Minimize the distance to the device if applicable. If the device was found, it can be paired. If there is a prompt for a password, follow the instructions of the manufacturer or type in the password. If the process is finished, go back to the LaRoomy app. The desired device should now appear in the list.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P4">4. By tapping the add button behind the device name in the list, the device will be added to the saved devices.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P5">5. The device is now saved and can be used, even it is not paired anymore.</string>

    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding">Device-Binding</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_H1">What is device-binding?</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_P1">By default everyone with the LaRoomy App installed is able to connect to every compatible remote device. To make the connection to your device private, device-binding could be enabled. A random generated, unique internal binding code will be transmitted to the remote device and (if supported by the device) is then required for further connections to the device.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_H2">What if more than one person wants to use a private device?</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_P2">The originator of the device-binding can share the binding-data with other persons by clicking the share button on the device-settings page. A share link will be generated. The binding-data will be encrypted and is device specific. The receiver is not able to connect to another device of the originator, even though the binding is generated with the same binding key.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_H3">What is the purpose of the custom binding key?</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_P3">The default binding key is hidden and not visible to a user. Its lifetime is limited to the lifetime of the application data. If an apps data is set back to default, the key will be generated new. To keep the key over that lifetime you can set your own key and note it somewhere for secure.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_H4">Important Notes:</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding_P4">Shared binding-data cannot be shared again by the receiver, only the originator is able to do that. And only the originator of the device-binding is able to unbind it.</string>

    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectionProcess_HeaderText">Connection process</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectionProcess_P1">By tapping a device in the list on the start-page the connection process will be started.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectionProcess_P2">As soon as a device is successful connected, the app will request a initialization package which contains basic data like the amount of device-properties or if a device binding is required. If device-binding is required, an authentication request will be sent.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectionProcess_P3">In the next step the device properties will be requested. If this process is complete they will be shown and can be used. If set up in the app settings, the properties will be locally saved for a specific device to provide a faster experience in future connections with this device. The saved properties can be deleted under \'Settings > Reset App\'.</string>

    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_UUIDProfiles_HeaderText">UUID Profiles</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_UUIDProfiles_P1">To exchange data via Bluetooth over GATT(Generic Attribute Profile) a service- and a characteristic UUID is required. If the required UUIDs differ from the default-definitions, the existing UUID-Profiles can be extended (when the service and characteristic UUID of the device are at hand).</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_UUIDProfiles_P2">Go to \'Settings > Manage UUID Profiles\' to review the existing profiles or add your own ones.</string>

    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_AppReset_HeaderText">Reset settings and data</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_AppReset_P1">All settings and local saved data can be partially or complete deleted. To do that, go to \'Settings > Reset App\' and select the data you want to reset or delete.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_AppReset_P2">Be careful when resetting the default binding key. If it is reset, a new internal key will be generated. If there are existing bindings to devices which require the old key, the connection process with these devices will fail.</string>

    <string name="UUIDProfileActivity_HeaderText">UUID Profiles</string>

    <string name="ViewLogActivity_HeaderText">Connection Log</string>
    <string name="ViewLogActivity_NotificationNoLogDataAvailable">No Log-Data available</string>
    <string name="ViewLogActivity_NotificationLoggingIsDisabled">Log creation is disabled</string>

    <string name="DataSharingActivity_GoToMainButtonText">Back to App</string>
    <string name="DataSharingActivity_BindingDataSuccessfulSet">Binding Data successful saved.</string>
    <string name="DataSharingActivity_Error_BindingDataInvalidFormat">Error: Invalid data format.</string>
    <string name="DataSharingActivity_Message_YouAreOriginator">You are the originator of the device binding. Implementing the key as a sharing receiver is not necessary.</string>

    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHeaderPlaceholderText">UUID Profile</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHeaderEditModeText">Edit UUID Profile</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHeaderNewModeText">New UUID Profile</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityModeError">Invocation Error</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityServiceUUIDDescriptorText">Service UUID:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivitySingleCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">Characteristic UUID:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityRXCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">RX Characteristic UUID:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityTXCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">TX Characteristic UUID:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityProfileNameDefaultValue">My Profile 1</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityProfileNameDescriptorText">Profile Name:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHelpText">The entered UUID can only contain numbers 0 to 9, lowercase letters a to f and the hyphen. Watch out for the appropriate format. For Example: 0000f5ff&#8211;0000&#8211;1000&#8211;8000&#8211;00805f9b34fb To generate a Bluetooth default UUID: tap the text above the box. If distinct characteristics for RX and TX are used, be aware that the receiver(rx) here corresponds to the transmitter(tx) on the remote device and vice versa.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivitySaveButtonText">Save</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityDeleteButtonText">Delete</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityButtonTextDiscard">Discard</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityIsStaticProfileNotification">This is a static profile. Changes will take no effect. Add a new profile to define your own UUIDs.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityInvalidUUIDNotification">Invalid UUID-Format.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityProfileNameAlreadyExistNotification">Profile-Name already exist.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityUseDistinctCharacteristicsCheckBoxText">Use distinct characteristics for RX and TX</string>

    <string name="AddDeviceActivityHeaderText">Add new Device</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityBondingHintText">Devices must be paired to show up in the list. Go to Bluetooth settings to pair a device.</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityGotoBluetoothSettingsButtonText">Bluetooth Settings</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityDoNotShowAgainButtonText">Do not show again</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityScanResultHeaderText">Available</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityPairedDevicesHeaderText">Paired</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityPermissionRationaleText">To scan for Bluetooth-Devices the location permission is required. This is an Android system requirement. Actually this app is not using the location in any case. Grant permission?</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityPermissionRationaleTitleText">Permission required</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityDeclineButton">No thanks</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityMissingPermissionMessageHeaderText">Device-Scan failed. The required permission was not granted.</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityMissingPermissionMessageT2Text">What you now can do:</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityMissingPermissionResolutionText1">1. Go to settings and enable the missing permission for this app.</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceActivityMissingPermissionResolutionText2">2. If your device could be paired, go to settings and pair it. It will then appear in the list below.</string>


    <!-- content descriptions and labels -->
    <string name="AvailableDeviceListImageDescription">Image for the appropriate device identification</string>
    <string name="DeviceTypeHeaderImageDescription">Image for the appropriate device</string>
    <string name="DeviceTypeHeaderImageButtonDescription">Remove the device and select a new device</string>
    <string name="DeviceInfoSubHeaderImageDescription">Image for the additional device info</string>
    <string name="DevicePropertyListElementImageDescription">Image for the appropriate device property</string>
    <string name="NavigateForwardImageDescription">Image-Arrow to navigate forward</string>
    <string name="DeviceReConnectImageButtonDescription">ImageButton to open the device-settings</string>
    <string name="BackImageButtonDescription">Button with the purpose to navigate back to the deviceMainActivity</string>
    <string name="InformationImageDescription">Button to open the info-activity</string>
    <string name="SettingsImageDescription">Button to open the main-settings-activity</string>
    <string name="MainActivityHamburgerButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Open the main menu to go to sub-pages</string>
    <string name="ManageUUIDProfileActivityAddButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Add a new uuid profile</string>
    <string name="NavigatorControlActivityOkButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Send an OK command to the remote device</string>
    <string name="NavigatorControlActivityUpButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Send an Up command to the remote device</string>
    <string name="NavigatorControlActivityDownButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Send a Down command to the remote device</string>
    <string name="NavigatorControlActivityRightButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Send a right command to the remote device</string>
    <string name="NavigatorControlActivityLeftButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Send an left command to the remote device</string>
    <string name="MainActivityAddButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Add a new device to your list</string>
    <string name="DeviceMainActivityPropertyListDescription" translatable="false">Shows the properties of the remote device</string>
    <string name="AddDeviceListElementContentDescription" translatable="false">Adds the device to the known devices</string>
    <string name="GeneralBackButtonLabel" translatable="false">Goes back to previous activity</string>
    <string name="GeneralForwardButtonLabel" translatable="false">Navigates to the next activity</string>
    <string name="GeneralClearButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Clear the content</string>
    <string name="GeneralReloadButtonContentDescription" translatable="false">Reload the Content</string>
    <string name="UnlockControlActivityChangePinButtonLabel" translatable="false">Change the pin of the remote device</string>
    <string name="UnlockControlActivityLockImageLabel" translatable="false">This image indicates the lock-status of the remote device. If unlocked, the remote device can be locked by tapping this image.</string>
    <string name="UnlockControlActivityShowHidePinButtonLabel" translatable="false">Show or hide the pin by pressing this image</string>
    <string name="ViewLogActivityScrollUpButtonLabel" translatable="false">Scroll to the top</string>
    <string name="ViewLogActivityScrollDownButtonLabel" translatable="false">Scroll to the bottom</string>
    <string name="ViewLogActivityExportButtonLabel" translatable="false">Export the log</string>

    <!-- Activity Labels -->
    <string name="MainActivityLabel">Start-Activity of the LaRoomy App</string>
    <string name="LoadingActivityLabel">Activity shown during the initialization process</string>
    <string name="DeviceMainActivity">Activity to show the primary properties of the device</string>
    <!-- Errors -->
    <string name="Error_ConnectionFailed_NoDevice">No valid device found</string>
    <string name="Error_SavedBindingKeyIsEmpty">Binding Key loading failed. Key was empty.</string>
    <string name="Error_ResumeFailedDeviceNotReachable">Resuming connection failed: Device not reachable.</string>
    <string name="Error_ResumeFailedNoDevice">Resuming connection failed: No device.</string>
    <string name="Error_UnexpectedBindingKeyMissing">Unexpected error: Internal binding key is missing.</string>
    <string name="Error_UnknownError">Unknown error occurred.</string>
    <string name="Error_InitFailed_NoProperties">Initialization failed. Property count is zero.</string>
    <string name="Error_NoMatchingServicesFound">No service matching the defined UUIDs was found. May take a look at the UUID-Profiles to solve the problem.</string>
    <string name="Error_NoMatchingCharacteristicsFound">No characteristic(s) matching the defined UUIDs were found. May take a look at the UUID-Profiles to solve the problem.</string>


    <!-- FileKeys: -->
    <string name="FileKey_BLEManagerData" translatable="false">fileKeyBluetoothManagerData</string>
    <string name="FileKey_AppSettings" translatable="false">fileKeyApplicationSettingsData</string>
    <string name="FileKey_BindingPairs" translatable="false">fileKeyBindingPairData</string>
    <string name="FileKey_AddedDevices" translatable="false">fileKeyAddedDevices</string>

    <!-- DataKeys: -->
    <string name="DataKey_LastSuccessfulConnectedDeviceAddress" translatable="false">lastSuccessfulConnectedDeviceAddress</string>
    <string name="DataKey_AutoConnect" translatable="false">autoConnectValue</string>
    <string name="DataKey_DefaultRandomBindingPasskey" translatable="false">bindingPasskey</string>
    <string name="DataKey_CustomBindingPasskey" translatable="false">customBindingPasskey</string>
    <string name="DataKey_SaveProperties" translatable="false">saveProperties</string>
    <string name="DataKey_EnableLog" translatable="false">enableLogging</string>
    <string name="DataKey_BindingPairStartKey" translatable="false">bindingPairStartKey</string>
    <string name="DataKey_KeepScreenActive" translatable="false">keepScreenActiveKey</string>

    <!-- Working elements -->
    <string name="UniversalPlaceholderName">This is a Placeholder</string>
    <string name="ConnectedDevicePlaceholderName">Device Name</string>
    <string name="LaRoomyDevicePropertyNamePlaceholder">Device Property Placeholder</string>
    <string name="LevelIndicationTextPlaceholder">100%</string>
    <string name="PropertySubPagePlaceholder">This is a property Page</string>
    <string name="RGBPageColorSelectionInformation">Selected Color: </string>
    <string name="info_activity_placeholder">Info Activity</string>
    <string name="app_settings">App-Settings</string>
    <string name="binding_code_placeholder">h5G+s%gt</string>
    <string name="pinCodePlaceholder">*****</string>
    <string name="uuidProfileListPlaceholder" translatable="false">Profile Element</string>
    <string name="UUIDFormatHint" translatable="false">0000ffff–0000-1000-8000-00805f9b34fb</string>
    <string name="UUIDDefaultFill" translatable="false">00000000-0000-1000-8000-00805f9b34fb</string>
    <string name="ConnectionLog_NoContent">Nothing to show..</string>
    <string name="TextResourceErrorState" translatable="false">Resource::Error</string>
    <string name="TextListPresenterListElementPlaceholderText">List Element</string>

</resources>
