<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LaRoomy</string>
    <string name="app_version">App-Version 2.1.0</string>
    <!-- UI Strings -->
    <string name="MA_AvailableDevicesPresentationTextViewText">Select Device:</string>
    <string name="MA_NoAvailableDevices">No devices found. Please make sure the device is bonded to the system.</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_SettingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_InformationTitle">App-Info</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_HelpTitle">Help Topics</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_ShowLogTitle">Show Log</string>
    <string name="MA_PopUp_ReloadList">Reload List</string>

    <string name="CA_Connecting">Connecting..</string>
    <string name="CA_Connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="CA_Authenticate">Authenticate..</string>
    <string name="CA_AuthSuccess">Authentication success - Checking Device Properties</string>
    <string name="CA_BindingPasskeyRejected">Wrong binding-passkey: connection rejected</string>
    <string name="CA_BindingNotActivated">Binding required but not activated in App-Settings</string>
    <string name="CA_TimeoutForConnection">Timeout - Device not reachable</string>

    <string name="DMA_ConnectionStatus_disconnected">disconnected</string>
    <string name="DMA_ConnectionStatus_connected">connected</string>
    <string name="DMA_Ready">Ready</string>
    <string name="DMA_DeviceConnectionSuspended">Connection suspended</string>
    <string name="DMA_LoadingPropertiesUserInfo">Loading Properties..</string>
    <string name="DMA_NoConnection">No connection</string>


    <string name="RGB_HeaderText">RGB Control</string>
    <string name="RGB_OnOff">On / Off</string>
    <string name="RGB_SingleColorModeButtonText">Single Color</string>
    <string name="RGB_TransitionModeButtonText">Transition</string>
    <string name="RGB_TransitionSpeedSeekBarText">Transition Speed</string>
    <string name="RGB_SoftTransitionSwitchText">Soft Transition</string>

    <string name="ELS_HeaderText">Ex Level Select</string>
    <string name="ELS_OnOff">On / Off</string>

    <string name="STS_HeaderText">Time Selector</string>
    <string name="STS_Hours">Hours</string>
    <string name="STS_Minutes">Minutes</string>
    <string name="STS_Seconds">Seconds</string>
    <string name="STS_TimePlaceholder">00 : 00</string>

    <string name="NavCon_HeaderText">Navigator</string>

    <string name="TFS_HeaderText">Time-Frame Selector</string>
    <string name="TFS_From">From</string>
    <string name="TFS_To">To</string>

    <string name="BGA_HeaderText">Bar Graph View</string>

    <string name="UnlockCtrl_HeaderText">Unlock Control</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ConditionText_Locked">Locked</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ConditionText_Unlocked">Unlocked - Tap Image to lock</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_PinEntryText">PIN:</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ButtonText_Show">Show</string>
    <string name="UnlockCtrl_ButtonText_Hide">Hide</string>


    <string name="GeneralMessage_reconnected">Device reconnected</string>
    <string name="GeneralMessage_connectionSuspended">Connection suspended</string>
    <string name="GeneralMessage_connectingFailed">Connection failed:</string>
    <string name="GeneralString_OK">OK</string>
    <string name="GeneralString_Cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="InfoActivity_HeaderText">LaRoomy</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_AppDescription">Dynamic Remote Control</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_AppVersionEntry">App-Version </string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CopyrightLaroomySoft">&#169; 2021 Laroomy-Soft</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_CEOHansZimmermann">CEO Hans Philipp Zimmermann</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_AllRightsReserved">All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_MailTo">info@laroomy.de</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PrivacyPolicyHeader">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PrivacyPolicy_Text">Laroomy-Soft(Hans Philipp Zimmermann) built the LaRoomy app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Hans Philipp Zimmermann at no cost and is intended for use as is.This page is used to inform users regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service. If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_InformationCollectionAndUse_Header">Information Collection and Use</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_InformationCollectionAndUse_Text">The app does not collect any personal data. But the app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ThirdPartyServiceLink_one">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LogDataHeader">Log Data</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LogDataText">I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LinksToOtherSitesHeader">Links to Other Sites</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_LinksToOtherSitesText">This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ChangesToThisPrivacyPolicyHeader">Changes to This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ChangesToThisPrivacyPolicyText">I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. This policy is effective as of 2020&#8211;09&#8211;09</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ContactUsHeader">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_PP_ContactUsText">If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at info@laroomy.de.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_HeaderText">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_FirstChapter">By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Hans Philipp Zimmermann. Hans Philipp Zimmermann is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for. The LaRoomy app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, in order to provide my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the LaRoomy app won’t work properly or at all. The app does use third party services that declare their own Terms and Conditions. Link to Terms and Conditions of third party service providers used by the app:</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_SecondChapter">You should be aware that there are certain things that Hans Philipp Zimmermann will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but Hans Philipp Zimmermann cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left. If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app. Along the same lines, Hans Philipp Zimmermann cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Hans Philipp Zimmermann cannot accept responsibility. With respect to Hans Philipp Zimmermann’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Hans Philipp Zimmermann accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app. At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Hans Philipp Zimmermann does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ChangesToThisTermsHeaderText">Changes to this Terms and Conditions</string>
    +
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ChangesToThisTermsContentText">I may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page. These terms and conditions are effective as of 2020–09–09</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ContactHeaderText">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="InfoActivity_TS_ContactContentText">If you have any questions or suggestions about my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact me at info@laroomy.de.</string>

    <string name="SetupActivity_Header">Settings</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_AutoConnectElementText">Auto-Connect</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_AutoConnectHint">If auto-connect is set up, the app will try to connect to the last device on startup. If only one device is available, the app connects automatically to this device.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_CustomBindingCodeElementText">Use custom binding key</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_CustomBindingCodeHint">By default a random generated binding-code is used. To use your own key, set it up here.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_BindingCodeDescriptor">Binding-Code</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_ListAllDevicesElementText">List all bluetooth devices</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_ListAllDevicesHint">If activated, the app will list all bonded Bluetooth- devices. By default, only devices corresponding to the LaRoomy naming conventions are listed.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_UUIDManagerButtonText">Manage UUID-Profiles</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_EnableLoggingElementText">Enable Connection Log</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_EnableLoggingHint">All transmission-data and connection-events will be saved to a temporary cache. This may reduce the performance in the connection process but could be helpful during the development process of the remote device.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_ShowLogButtonText">Show Log</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_PassKeyMustNotBeEmpty">Binding Code cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_PassKeyMaxIs10Character">The maximum length of the binding-code is 10 character.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_PassKeyContainsInvalidCharacter">The binding-code contains invalid character.</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_ResetDataButtonText">Reset App Data</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_KeepScreenActiveElementText">Keep screen active</string>
    <string name="SetupActivity_KeepScreenActiveHint">Prevents the device from falling in sleep-mode when the remote device is connected.</string>

    <string name="ResetAppActivity_HeaderText">Reset Data</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_SelectDataActionText">Select the data you want to reset:</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_SelectAllCheckBoxText">Select all</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetAppSettingsCheckBoxText">App Settings</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetBindingDataCheckBoxText">Binding Data</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetUUIDProfilesCheckBoxText">UUID Profiles</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetDefaultBindingKeyCheckBoxText">Default Binding Key</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetAppSettingsCheckBoxHint">The common app settings will be set to default.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetBindingDataCheckBoxHint">All data regarding the device-binding will be deleted. Including the shared binding data.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetUUIDProfilesCheckBoxHint">All UUID-Profiles will be deleted. Except the static profiles.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetDefaultBindingKeyCheckBoxHint">A new custom Binding-Key will be generated. Be careful if there are remote devices which require the current Key.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_CancelButtonText">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_ResetButtonText">Reset</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_NoDataSelected">No data selected.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogMessage">The selected data will be deleted or restored to default.</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogTitle">Reset</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogPositiveButtonText">OK</string>
    <string name="ResetAppActivity_DialogNegativeButtonText">Cancel</string>


    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_HeaderText">Device-Settings</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_UserInfo_Connected">Device Connected</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_UserInfo_Disconnected">Device Disconnected</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingSwitchDescriptor">Enable Binding</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingPurposeHintForEnable">When activating, a binding-request will be sent to the remote device. If supported by the device, your binding-code will be written to the device and is necessary for all subsequent connections.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingPurposeHintForDisable">When deactivating, a binding-release-request will be sent to the remote device. If successful, the device accepts all connections.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetButtonDescriptorText">Factory Reset</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetButtonText">Reset</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetConfirmationMessage">The remote device will be restored to the default configuration. Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ShareButtonDescriptorText">Share Device-Binding</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_ShareButtonHint">The binding information for this specific device will be shared. The data will be encrypted and your binding-code is not visible to the receiver or someone else.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_FactoryResetHint">A factory-reset-command will be sent to the remote device.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingNotSupportedNotification">The connected device does not support binding.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_OnlyTheOriginCanShareTheBindingNotification">The connection with this device is established with a shared binding-key. Sharing a shared key is not possible, only the originator is able to share the binding.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_OnlyTheOriginCanReleaseTheBinding">The connection with this device is established with a shared binding-key. Only the originator is able to release the binding.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingSuccessNotification">Binding successful generated.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_BindingErrorNotification">Binding failure. Error occurred on the device.</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceInfoHeaderText"><u>Device Info:</u></string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceInfoNameDescriptorText">Name:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceMACAddressDescriptorText">MAC:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceServiceUUIDDescriptorText">Service UUID:</string>
    <string name="DeviceSettingsActivity_DeviceCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">Characteristic UUID:</string>


    <string name="AppHelpActivityHeaderText">Help-Topics</string>
    <string name="AppHelpTopic_ConnectDevice">Connect new device</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivityGotoBluetoothButtonText">Goto Bluetooth Settings</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_Explanation">To get the remote device showing up in the list on the start page, the device must be bonded.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P1">1. Make sure the remote device is reachable. If not, decrease the distance to the device.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P2">2. Go to the Bluetooth-Settings on your device and scan for nearby devices.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P3">3. If the desired device is found, click on it to create bond. You may will be asked for a bonding password. Usually it is something like 000000 or 123456.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_ConnectDevice_P4">4. When the device is successfully bonded, open the laroomy app. The device should now be listed.</string>
    <string name="AppHelpActivity_Topic_DeviceBinding">Device-Binding</string>

    <string name="UUIDProfileActivity_HeaderText">UUID Profiles</string>

    <string name="ViewLogActivity_HeaderText">Connection Log</string>
    <string name="ViewLogActivity_NotificationNoLogDataAvailable">No Log-Data available</string>

    <string name="DataSharingActivity_GoToMainButtonText">Back to App</string>
    <string name="DataSharingActivity_BindingDataSuccessfulSet">Binding Data successful saved.</string>
    <string name="DataSharingActivity_Error_BindingDataInvalidFormat">Error: Invalid data format.</string>

    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHeaderPlaceholderText">UUID Profile</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHeaderEditModeText">Edit UUID Profile</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHeaderNewModeText">New UUID Profile</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityModeError">Invocation Error</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityServiceUUIDDescriptorText">Service UUID:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityCharacteristicUUIDDescriptorText">Characteristic UUID:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityProfileNameDefaultValue">My Profile 1</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityProfileNameDescriptorText">Profile Name:</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityHelpText">The entered UUID can only contain numbers 0 to 9, lowercase letters a to f and the hyphen. Watch out for the appropriate format. For Example: 0000f5ff&#8211;0000&#8211;1000&#8211;8000&#8211;00805f9b34fb To generate a Bluetooth default UUID: tap the text above the box.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivitySaveButtonText">Save</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityDeleteButtonText">Delete</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityButtonTextDiscard">Discard</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityIsStaticProfileNotification">This is a static profile. Changes will take no effect. Add a new profile to define your own UUIDs.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityInvalidUUIDNotification">Invalid UUID-Format.</string>
    <string name="EditUUIDProfileActivityProfileNameAlreadyExistNotification">Profile-Name already exist.</string>

    <!-- Image content descriptions -->
    <string name="AvailableDeviceListImageDescription">Image for the appropriate device identification</string>
    <string name="DeviceTypeHeaderImageDescription">Image for the appropriate device</string>
    <string name="DeviceTypeHeaderImageButtonDescription">Button to remove the device and select a new device</string>
    <string name="DeviceInfoSubHeaderImageDescription">Image for the additional device info</string>
    <string name="DevicePropertyListElementImageDescription">Image for the appropriate device property</string>
    <string name="NavigateForwardImageDescription">Image-Arrow to navigate forward</string>
    <string name="DeviceReConnectImageButtonDescription">ImageButton to open the device-settings</string>
    <string name="BackImageButtonDescription">Button with the purpose to navigate back to the deviceMainActivity</string>
    <string name="InformationImageDescription">Button to open the info-activity</string>
    <string name="SettingsImageDescription">Button to open the main-settings-activity</string>
    <!-- Labels -->
    <string name="MainActivityLabel">Start-Activity of the LaRoomy App</string>
    <string name="LoadingActivityLabel">Activity shown during the initialization process</string>
    <string name="DeviceMainActivity">Activity to show the primary properties of the device</string>
    <!-- Errors -->
    <string name="Error_ConnectionFailed_NoDevice">No valid device found</string>
    <string name="Error_SavedBindingKeyIsEmpty">Binding Key loading failed. Key was empty.</string>


    <!-- FileKeys: -->
    <string name="FileKey_BLEManagerData" translatable="false">fileKeyBluetoothManagerData</string>
    <string name="FileKey_AppSettings" translatable="false">fileKeyApplicationSettingsData</string>
    <string name="FileKey_BindingPairs" translatable="false">fileKeyBindingPairData</string>

    <!-- DataKeys: -->
    <string name="DataKey_LastSuccessfulConnectedDeviceAddress" translatable="false">lastSuccessfulConnectedDeviceAddress</string>
    <string name="DataKey_UseCustomBindingKey" translatable="false">useDeviceBindingValue</string>
    <string name="DataKey_AutoConnect" translatable="false">autoConnectValue</string>
    <string name="DataKey_DefaultRandomBindingPasskey" translatable="false">bindingPasskey</string>
    <string name="DataKey_CustomBindingPasskey" translatable="false">customBindingPasskey</string>
    <string name="DataKey_ListAllDevices" translatable="false">listAllDevicesValue</string>
    <string name="DataKey_EnableLog" translatable="false">enableLogging</string>
    <string name="DataKey_BindingPairStartKey" translatable="false">bindingPairStartKey</string>
    <string name="DataKey_KeepScreenActive" translatable="false">keepScreenActiveKey</string>

    <!-- Working elements -->
    <string name="UniversalPlaceholderName">This is a Placeholder</string>
    <string name="ConnectedDevicePlaceholderName">Device Name</string>
    <string name="LaRoomyDevicePropertyNamePlaceholder">Device Property Placeholder</string>
    <string name="LevelIndicationTextPlaceholder">100%</string>
    <string name="PropertySubPagePlaceholder">This is a property Page</string>
    <string name="RGBPageColorSelectionInformation">Selected Color: </string>
    <string name="info_activity_placeholder">Info Activity</string>
    <string name="app_settings">App-Settings</string>
    <string name="binding_code_placeholder">h5G+s%gt</string>
    <string name="pinCodePlaceholder">*****</string>
    <string name="uuidProfileListPlaceholder" translatable="false">Profile Element</string>
    <string name="UUIDFormatHint" translatable="false">0000ffff–0000-1000-8000-00805f9b34fb</string>
    <string name="UUIDDefaultFill" translatable="false">00000000-0000-1000-8000-00805f9b34fb</string>
    <string name="ConnectionLog_NoContent">Nothing to show..</string>

</resources>
